#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

# **Wei Yan**

202-6688 ARCOLA ST, BURNABY, V5E 0B3 587-439-8687 WEIYAN.CA@ICLOUD.COM WWW.LINKEDIN.COM/IN/YAN-WEI-CA

#### **PROFILE**

Associate, enthusiastic and highly motivated developer with passion and more than two years' experience in efficiently coding websites and applications using modern HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node. Translate designs to front-end code. Eager to embrace challenges and learn more.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

PLAYGON INTERACTIVE INC.

MARCH 2021-PRESENT / VANCOUVER, BC / REMOTE

## Tech Stack: React, Redux, styled-component, webSocket, react-transition-group, JIRA

- Developed and maintaining premium game experience web application. Focusing on different animations for presenting a high UX performance.
- Lead a migration from javascript to typescript for an integration with service platform which provides better maintenance.
- Able to solve tricky issues on cross browser debugging. Implement components to
  fulfill different features like fullscreen, scroll, router, etc. Designed and implemented
  a hash-based localization process to improve translation process and support.

### FRONTEND DEVELOPER

FANTUAN

JULY 2020 - MARCH 2021 / BURNABY, BC

# Tech Stack: React-Native, TypeScript, React-Navigation, Restful API, Stripe

- Built multi-end, responsive and stable mobile/h5 applications of Fantuan Reviews Platform in fast paces.
- Implemented UIs follows pixel level. Handled multi-tasks and delivered on time.
- Developed checkout solutions for processing different payment.

# FREELANCE DEVELOPER

NGX INTERACTIVE / WOOHELPS INTERNATIONAL TECHNOLOGY MAY-2019 - JULY 2020 / REMOTE

# Tech Stack: Gatsby.js GraphQL, javascript, HTML 5, CSS

- Converted a tablet application to a web application with same experience, and also provided responsive behaviour to support mobile version.
- Developed and deployed dynamic and user-friendly pages on different platforms.

# **EDUCATION**

Shenyang Aerospace University, China – Bachelor's degree of Computer Science

### **SKILLS**

- Languages: Typescript, Javascript, HTML, CSS
- Libraries: React, Redux, React-Native, Express
- Apis: Restful, webSocket, GraphQL
- Tools: Git, NPM, Agile/Scrum, VsCode
- Testing: Jest, React Testing Library